<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Robin (axcelott)</title>
  <subtitle>Thoughts and opinions of a teenager from the Netherlands.</subtitle>
  <id>https://roblog.nl/</id>
  <link href="https://roblog.nl/" />
  <author>
    <name>Robin Boers</name>
    <email>webmaster@roblog.nl</email>
  </author>
  <rights>Made with ♡ in the Netherlands. Copying is an act of love. Please copy.</rights>
  <link href="https://roblog.nl/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />

  <!-- INSERT NEW POSTS HERE -->
  <entry>
    <title>Movies and Limited Series</title>
    <link href="https://roblog.nl/blog/good-movies" />
    <published>2024-02-07T12:00:00+01:00</published>
    <id>https://roblog.nl/blog/good-movies</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[ <p>So lately I've been watching a lot of Netflix.</p>
      <p>
        Generally I'm not the kind of person that consumes a lot of media. I'd
        rather make things; I find creating things way more satisfying.
      </p>

      <p>
        However, I got a bit burned out in terms of ideas — I didn't know what
        to build — enery, and time (school am I right ✨). So, instead I spent
        about 20 hours of my life staring at a screen, looking at fictional
        characters living their almost perfect made-up lives.
      </p>

      <p>Anyways, I really enjoyed these in particular:</p>

      <ul>
        <li>After</li>
        <li>Tick, tick… BOOM!</li>
        <li>Heartstopper</li>
        <li>Inventing Anna</li>
        <li>Bohemian Rhapsody</li>
        <li>Love, Rosie</li>
        <li>Friends with Benefits</li>
        <li>Lady Chatterley's Lover</li>
        <li>The Girl Nextdoor</li>
        <li>Queen's Gambit</li>
        <li>Don't Look Up</li>
        <li>Dirty Lines</li>
        <li>The Social Network</li>
        <li>The Playlist</li>
        <li>The Social Dilemma</li>
        <li>Yesterday</li>
        <li>I Used to Be Famous</li>
        <li>We Are the Wave</li>
      </ul>

      <p>
        I really enjoyed the mini series in particular; it allows the filmmaker
        to tell a more detailed story, yet it doesn't require as much time (and
        commitment) to watch, opposed to, forexample, a 7-season-long show.
      </p>

      <p>
        A movie feels short when you're used to a series. But that's part of the
        appeal I think. A movie doesn't try to suck you in, like a series does.
        It just tells a story.
      </p>

      <details>
        <summary>Context</summary>
        <p>
          I wrote this a while back (somewhere fall last year), but I forgot to
          publish it. I found the draft yesterday.
        </p>

        <p>
          Also, a lot of movies listed above share one common theme: they're all
          semi-related to the reproductive system; I'm a teenager, after all ;)
        </p>
      </details> ]]></content>
  </entry>

</feed>